RG 183, Connecticut River Valley Flood Control Commission
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Directors' Files, 1953-1982
  - Director Philip Shutler Files, 1953-1968
    - Statements/testimony to Congress, 1954-1968 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Thames River Basin, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - U.S. Attorney (District of Vermont), 1959 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - WD pix, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Director Nathan Tufts Files, 1968-1982
    - Connecticut River picture, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Connecticut Watershed Council and publications, 1947-1952 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Corps Of Engineers acquisition reports, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Corps Of Engineers, 1964-1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Corps Of Engineers, 1971-1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Corps Of Engineers, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1972 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, clippings, 1968-1972 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - 1969-1970 correspondence, Hull testimony, 1953-1970 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, member of the CRVFCC, 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 37-40)
    - Correspondence/notes, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Death of Philip Shutler and eulogy, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Flood meeting, 1969 September 27 - December 12 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Gordon Ainsworth and Associates, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Hand drawn map - of victory bog, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Lists of acreage acquired for flood control dams from Corps of Engineers, 1970-1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Meeting prep, 1970 September 25 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Membership of Massachusetts Steering Committee of the Connecticut River, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Merrimack River Valley Flood Control Commission Board of Arbitration reports, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1961-1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - N.E. Governor's Conference/N.E. and N.Y. Water Council, 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - New England River Basin Commission, 1969-1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - New England River Basin Commission, 1961-1981 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - New England River Basin Commission, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Newsletter, 1968-1982 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Newsletter, Essays on River, 1968-1981 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Newsletter / mailing to CRVFCC, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Prep for June 20 meeting, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Shutler ceremony, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Tufts newsletter, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Series 3. Executive Secretary Files, 1982-2003
  - Executive Secretary Pauline Smiaroski Files, 1982-2003
    - Reports to commission, 1982-2003 (Box 6, Folder 22-24)
    - Resources, 1983-1991 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Steno notebook, 1981 May 4 - 1981 June 25 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Steno notebook, 1981 June 25 - September 16 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Steno notebook, 1981 September 17 - November 20 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Steno notebook, 1981 November 20 - 1985 June 14 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Series 4. Reports and Studies, 1954-2010
  - Ainsworth report and correspondence, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 10-11)
  - Annual report, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Two year annual report, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Bi-annual report, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Bi-annual report, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Bi-annual report, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Annual report, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Annual report, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Annual report, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Annual report, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Annual report, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Annual report, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Annual report, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Annual report, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Annual report, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Annual report, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Annual report, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Annual report, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Annual report, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Annual report, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Annual report, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Annual report, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Annual report fiscal year, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Annual report, 1956-1991 (Box 19, Folder 3-5)
    Duplicate copies of annual reports.
  - Brief relative to federal river and harbor projects within Massachusetts, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Connecticut River Basin Comprehensive Investigation, Executive Session, Coordinating Committee, Subcommittee on Data Processing, Key word method for data abstract storage and retrieval, 1967 May 10 (Box 18)
  - Connecticut River Basin in the 1980's: Challenges and opportunities, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Connecticut River comprehensive water resources investigation, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Connecticut River National Recreation Area feasibility study, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Draft of annual report, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Draft Report of BSCE Subcommittee on Flood Frequency, Flood Potential Magnitude and Flood Formulas, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee meeting report Connecticut River Watershed Council, 1970 September 10 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Executive secretary reports, 1982-1989 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Fiscal year, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - H.J. Cadwell report, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - National Valley Storage, 1989-1994 (Box 7, Folder 56-57)
  - New Hampshire Water Resources Board, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - North Atlantic Regional water and related land resources study, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Ferrick, Michael G., George E. Lemieux, Patricia B. Weyrick, and Warren Demont. CRREL Report 88-1, Options for management of dynamic ice breakup on the Connecticut River near Windsor, Vermont. US Army Corps of Engineers Cold Research & Engineering Laboratory, 1988 March (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Preview Connecticut River Basin study, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Proposal for water resource management in Connecticut River Basin, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Quabbin/Connecticut River study, 1982-1992 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Reports, theses, and technical data on flood control from Library of Congress, undated (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
  - Schedule of requests to Congress to provide for construction of dams, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Willis, Philip W. Some Economic and Social Effects of the North Springfield Flood Control Dam in the Town of Weathersfield, Vermont, circa 1964-1965, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Sunset reports summary, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - The Nature of Connecticut, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Weather emergency reporting and flood control: a special report, 1997 December (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Weather emergency reporting and flood control, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Series 5. Subject Files, 1935-2010
  - Reservoirs and Dams
    - Ball Mountain, 1955-1957 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Ball Mountain ceremonies, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Ball Mountain contracts and construction, 1956-1960 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Maps removed from folder to Series 10. Maps, Box 21.
    - Ball Mountain Jamaica Londonderry, 1956-1964 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Ball Mountain tax losses, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Barre Falls, 1954-1958 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Beaver Brook reservoir, 1965-1972 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Bloomfield, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Brockway Mills Dam, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Buffumville Dam - Little River Thames Massachusetts, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Chicopee local protection project, 1963-2002 (Box 8, Folder 23-24)
    - Chicopee River, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Claremont Reservoir, 1965-1969 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Cold River, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Colebrook Dam and Reservoir, Sandfield, Massachusetts, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Colebrook River Dam and Reservoir, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Communities with local protection projects in the Connecticut River Valley, 1989-1996 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Conant Brook Reservoir, 1959-1966 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Dam dedications, 1956-1969 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Deerfield River Dam, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - East Barre Dam, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Farmington River, 1956-1960 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Gaysville Dam River, 1956-1969 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Littleville Dam, 1956-1965 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Littleville Dam, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Littleville dedication, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Littleville flood control dam, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - North Hartland Dam dedication, 1957-1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - North Springfield, Vermont clippings, 1957-1960 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - North Springfield flood control dam, Black River watershed, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Obstinate facts and figures reservoirs, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Otter Brook, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Otter Brook ceremony, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Dedication - Otter Brook October 3, 1958, 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Otter Brook recreation area, 1954-1958 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Upper Naugatuck River, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Victory Dam, 1959-1964 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Victory Dam, 1959-1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Victory Dam, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Waterbury Dam, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Westfield River, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - West River at Weston, Vermont, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Work lists, etc., all dam areas, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Corps Flood Control Dam Commission, 1972-1979 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - CRVFCC seal, 1948-1968 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission, 1983-2004 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Funding increase, 1987-1995 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Gabions, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - General correspondence, 1970-2004 (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
  - Legislation, 1935-1982 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Legislation, 1955-1977 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Legislation, 1938-1964 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Letters to governors, senators, etc., 1980-1999 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Letters to governors, senators, etc., 1996-2006 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Massachusetts State Library, 1989-2010 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of 23rd meeting of coordinating committee, Connecticut River comprehensive water resources investigation, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of 24th meeting of coordinating committee, Connecticut River comprehensive water resources investigation, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Moran Brief, 1957 Mass. Acts 1895/6/8 and 1927 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - New England Regional Commission, 1967-1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - River Forecast Center, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Resolution, 1995 December 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Sunset Review Committee, New Hampshire, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Series 6. Press Files, 1936-1998
  - Vicki French-Lankarge, "An Appreciation of The Beautiful River, the Connecticut, that Nourished Settlement and Culture Along its Banks, Especially on Its Course Through Hampshire County." A Special Bicentennial Report for the Daily Hampshire Gazette, 1986 September 19-25 (Box 18)
  - Clippings, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1958 April-September (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1958 March-April (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1958 March-April (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1958 April-May (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1958 May-June (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1970-1971, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Clippings - division, non-structural, alternatives, 1975-1981 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Clippings - flood control, 1953-1959 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Clippings from Joe Knox, 1954-1956 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Clippings - power projects, environment, 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Spring run-off, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Flood, Holyoke, 1936 March (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - New England News Clip Agency, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Series 7. Financial Records, 1935-2007
  - Economic Losses, Tax Losses, and Repayments
    - A.G. Dewey Co. potential economic losses covered by CRVFCC, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - A.G. Dewey Co., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Birch Hill final, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Birch Hill general, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Birch Hill - Royalston, worksheets, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Birch Hill - Templeton, worksheets, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Birch Hill - Winchendun, worksheets, 1954-1957 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Central, Massachusetts, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Commonwealth of Massachusetts: standard terms and conditions, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence discrepancy in tax loss figures, 1977-1948 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Final figures on valuations for Weathersfield, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Hartford - 1961 tax loss (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - History of tax loss reimbursement payments, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Jamaica, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Knightville, final valuations, Chesterfield and Huntington, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Knightville, general, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Knightville Reservoir, Chesterfield and Huntington, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Littleville Dam, Huntington and Chester, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Littleville property, 1956-1960 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - North Hartland, Vermont, 1956-1958 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - North Hartland, Vermont, 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - North Hartland, Vermont dam - Hartford, 1959-1965 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - North Hartland Dam - Hartland, 1958-1963 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - North Hartland reaction of owners to purchase method, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - North Hartland Reservoir property taking, 1956-1961 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - North Springfield, Vermont, 1955-1961 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - North Springfield Dam - Springfield, 1957-1964 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - North Springfield Dam - Weathersfield and Perkinsville, 1960-1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Opinions of Attorney General re. tax loss reimbursement formula, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Otter Brook, 1954-1961 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Otter Brook, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Otter Brook Dam - Keene and Roxbury, 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Otter Brook, tax losses, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Report of Philip W. Willis (North Springfield flood control dam), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Revaluations on properties taken for flood control projects from date of taking, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Review - personal property tax, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Signed agreements on property valuations (flood control), 1958-1964 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - State's payments tax losses, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - State Treasurer - Connecticut economic losses, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - State Treasurer - Massachusetts economic loses, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - State Treasurer - Vermont economic losses, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - State Treasurer - Connecticut economic losses, 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - State Treasurer - Massachusetts economic loses, 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - State Treasurer - New Hampshire economic losses, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - State Treasurer - Vermont economic losses, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - State Treasurer - Connecticut economic losses and repayments, 1956-1961 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - State Treasurer - Connecticut tax losses and repayments, 1962-1972 (Box 11, Folder 28-29)
    - State Treasurer - New Hampshire tax losses and repayments, 1957-1972 (Box 11, Folder 30-32)
    - State Treasurer - Massachusetts tax losses and repayments, 1957-1972 (Box 11, Folder 33-35)
    - State Treasurer - Vermont tax losses and repayments, 1957-1961 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - State Treasurer - Vermont tax losses and repayments, 1962-1966 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - State Treasurer - Vermont tax losses and repayments, 1967-1972 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Surry Mountain final valuations, 1947-1954 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Surry Mountain worksheets, 1939-1958 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Taxes, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Taxes, 1960-1969 (Box 11, Folder 42-51)
    - Tax loss figures, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Tax loss formula, 1961-1970 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Tax loss formula adjustments, 1969-1982 (Box 11, Folder 54-55)
    - Revaluation/tax rate letter, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Tax loss reimbursement matters, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Tax losses at reservoirs by states, 1953-1960 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Tax losses and repayments, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Tax losses by town, 1954-1961 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Tax losses, 1954-1956 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Tax losses, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    - Tax losses, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Tax losses worksheets, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Tax losses towns, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Tax losses and repayments, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Tax losses worksheets, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Tax losses and repayments, 1960-1966 (Box 12, Folder 10-16)
    - Tax losses worksheets, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Tax losses and repayments, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Tax losses worksheets, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Tax losses and repayments, 1968-1974 (Box 12, Folder 20-26)
    - Tax losses and reimbursements, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Tax losses and repayments, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 28-30)
    - Tax losses and reimbursements, 1979-2001 (Box 12, Folder 31-53)
    - Tax losses and reimbursements, 2002-2007 (Box 13, Folder 1-6)
    - Tax reimbursement letters, Connecticut, 1973-1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Tax reimbursement letters, Massachusetts, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Tax reimbursement letters, New Hampshire, 1973-1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Tax reimbursement letters, Vermont, 1973-1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Thetford and Norwich and Union Village final correspondence, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Townshend Dam - Jamaica, 1958-1964 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Townshend Dam - Townshend, 1958-1964 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Townshend valuation losses, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Townshend, Vermont reservoir, 1956-1959 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Tully and Athol worksheets, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Tully, final, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Tully and Royalston worksheet, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Union Village copies, 1954-1959 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Union Village worksheets, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - U.S. Dept. of Interior Public Law 94-565, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Vermont benefits accruing annually from new reservoirs, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Claims
    - A.G. Dewey Company, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - A.G. Dewey Company, claim report, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Ballard claim (North Heartland flood control Dam), 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Claims Hearing: Capron, Brown, Harvey Hartland, Vermont, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Claims - Mines, Adams, Beardman, Church and Costello (North Hartland), 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Claims - North Hartland, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Committee on claims, 1959-1961 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence in re. to Hartland claims countermarch, et. al., 1958-1961 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Dickie, Logan and Kathleen - Petition North Hartland, Vermont, dam, 1958-1966 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Dickie, Logan and Kathleen, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Economic losses, 1953-1956 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Economic losses, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Economic losses claims to be paid, notifications of awards, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Economic losses payments, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Flood economic losses, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Heald Brothers - appraisal for North Hartland and Springfield dams, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Littleville economic loss claims, 1963-1968 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - North Springfield claims, 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 38-39)
    - North Springfield Dam claims, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - North Springfield economic loss claims, duplicates, 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Perkinsville Service Co. claims, 1956-1959 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Perkinsville Electric claims, 1956-1961 (Box 13, Folder 43-44)
    - Perkinsville Electric claims, 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Townshend - Decelle Co., 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Transcript of hearings, 1. North Springfield, 2. North Hartland, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Warren, Franklin claim (North Hartland flood control dam), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - West River Sand and Gravel Inc., 1957-1961 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
    - Whittemore, Gilbert - Perkinsville General Store (North Springfield flood control dam), 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Commission Finances
    - Accounts ledger, 1956-1965; 1 volume (Box Drawer 84, Folder Item 1)
    - Accounts ledger, 1969-1972; 1 volume (Box Drawer 84, Folder Item 2)
    - Appropriations for Connecticut River flood control dams, 1956-1958 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations for dams, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Bonds and insurance (old), 1969-1978 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Commission expenses, 1982-1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Handbook for state OASI administrators, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Insurance (old coverage and companies), 1979-1983 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Insurance basic liability, 1981-1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Massachusetts, payment, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Massachusetts state auditor correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Official audit report from state of Massachusetts, 1972-1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Official audit report from state of Massachusetts, 1954-1960 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - State payments to CRVFCC, 1954-1960 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - State contributions to CRVFCC, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 20-22)
    - State contributions to CRVFCC, 1977-1994 (Box 14, Folder 23-40)
    - Statement of cash receipts and disbursements, 1935-1990 (Box 14, Folder 41-43)
- Series 8. NENYIAC, 1952-1956
  - Brig. Gen. B.B. Talley, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Col. G.B.T., 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Economics, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Executive Council secretary's notes, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 48)